So what's new Mark?
How is your new job going To be
honest,
I can't complain. I really love the
company that I am working for. My
coworkers are all really friendly
and helpful. They really help me
feel welcome. It's a really
energetic and fun atmosphere.
My boss is hilarious.
And he's really flexible, really.
Really. How so?
He allows me to come in when I want
and make my own hours. I can also
leave early if I start early. There
is no real dress code either. I can
wear jeans and AT shirt if I want. I
can even wear shorts in the summer.
Wow.
It sounds really cool. I can't stand
wearing a suit every day.
Which do you prefer,
working late or finishing early?
I prefer finishing early. I really
enjoy the morning. I love getting up
early and going for a run. There's
nothing like watching the sunrise
while drinking my morning coffee.
Really. I am opposite.
I love sleeping in. I am most alert
in the evenings.
I'm a real night owl.
You know what they say,
the early bird catches the worm. You
could be right. Maybe I will try to
go to bed a little earlier tonight.